[{"answer": " There are so many options for things to do on campus.  I cant decide what to d", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " I know.  There are a lot of choices.  Im looking at all of the things offered by th", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 16, "question": " There are so many options for things to do on campus.  I cant decide what to d", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Do you think youll join a sports team or take a fitness class", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 21, "question": " I know.  There are a lot of choices.  Im looking at all of the things offered by th", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " I dont know.  I probably should  I think I got the freshman fifteen.  Im no", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Do you think youll join a sports team or take a fitness class", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " There are lots of other non-athletic options.  Look at this page.  There are ove", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 26, "question": " I dont know.  I probably should  I think I got the freshman fifteen.  Im no", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Yeah, they do.  It might be fun to join a student group like those.  I wonder if the", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 31, "question": " There are lots of other non-athletic options.  Look at this page.  There are ove", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " It says here that they meet once or twice a month", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Yeah, they do.  It might be fun to join a student group like those.  I wonder if the", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Thats not too bad.  Youd still have a lot of time for studying", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 39, "question": " It says here that they meet once or twice a month", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " True", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Thats not too bad.  Youd still have a lot of time for studying", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Im kind of interested in volunteering some time to work on the UGA yearbook o", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 41, "question": " True", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": "Oh, the DJ thing would be cool", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Im kind of interested in volunteering some time to work on the UGA yearbook o", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Doesnt that sound cool?  We should volunteer and try to have a radio sho", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Oh, the DJ thing would be cool", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Want to?  We could have an international music radio show and play music fro", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Doesnt that sound cool?  We should volunteer and try to have a radio sho", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Yeah.  Lets try to do that", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Want to?  We could have an international music radio show and play music fro", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " What does the brochure say about volunteering", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Yeah.  Lets try to do that", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " It gives you a number to call to get information.  Should I call it now", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 56, "question": " What does the brochure say about volunteering", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Yeah.  Call it", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 57, "question": " It gives you a number to call to get information.  Should I call it now", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Yeah.  Call it", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Yes, hi.  I was calling to ask about volunteering as a DJ at the radio station.  M", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 59, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " What did they say?  We cant do it", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Yes, hi.  I was calling to ask about volunteering as a DJ at the radio station.  M", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Nope.  They said they already have enough volunteers for next term.  We hav", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 66, "question": " What did they say?  We cant do it", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " That sucks", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Nope.  They said they already have enough volunteers for next term.  We hav", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " I know.  I guess they dont want our help", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 71, "question": " That sucks", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Well, now what are we going to do next term", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 72, "question": " I know.  I guess they dont want our help", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " I guess we could just do some of the other recreational activities on campus:  g", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Well, now what are we going to do next term", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " I guess so.  I kind of wanted to join a club or something though.  I might go to th", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 80, "question": " I guess we could just do some of the other recreational activities on campus:  g", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Yeah, maybe Ill go to the Business Club and check it out", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 84, "question": " I guess so.  I kind of wanted to join a club or something though.  I might go to th", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " We might as well try", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Yeah, maybe Ill go to the Business Club and check it out", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " We could do that this term, and then next term try the DJ thing", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 86, "question": " We might as well try", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " We should.  Having a radio show would be so cool", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 87, "question": " We could do that this term, and then next term try the DJ thing", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " OK, then its decided", "docId": "05-02", "aSentId": 88, "question": " We should.  Having a radio show would be so cool", "qSentId": 87}]
